<!DOCTYPE ui:UiBinder SYSTEM "http://dl.google.com/gwt/DTD/xhtml.ent">
<ui:UiBinder xmlns:ui='urn:ui:com.google.gwt.uibinder'
             xmlns:g='urn:import:com.google.gwt.user.client.ui'>
    <ui:style>
        .title {
            margin: 0 0 14px 0;
            font-size: 16pt;
        }
        .subtitle {
            margin: 24px 0 10px 0;
            font-size: 16pt;
        }
        .content {
            font-size: 12pt;
        }
        .content > b {
            font-size: 12pt;
        }
        .content > i {
            font-size: 12pt;
        }
        .content > a {
            font-size: 12pt;
            color: #000;
        }
    </ui:style>
    <g:HTMLPanel>
        <div class="{style.title}">Welcome to Busy Humans!</div>
        <div class="{style.content}">
            The place where you can share your activities with the world!<br/>
            <br/>
            Have you ever asked yourself:
        </div>
        <ul>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <i>Is anybody out there who would like to do _______?</i>
            </li>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <i>Has anybody ever done _______?</i>
            </li>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <i>Who is the best at _______?</i>
            </li>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <i>I am bored. What could I do?</i>
            </li>
        </ul>
        <div class="{style.content}">Busy Humans has all the answers, so take a look around and get busy :)</div>
        <div class="{style.subtitle}">How does it work?</div>
        <ul>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <b>Step 1: Login!</b> Use the Login button in the top right-hand corner to create your personal profile.
            </li>
            <br/>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <b>Step 2: Get busy!</b> Click the <a href="#discover">Challenges</a>-Tab to browse existing assignments.
                If you like an assignment and think that you could perform the activity, go ahead and do it.
                Take pictures or videos to share your experience.
            </li>
            <br/>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <b>Step 3: Get ratings!</b> People will rate your activity.
                Three days later, the ratings will be converted to experience points (XP) which are added to your account.
                Your total XP balance is used to determine your place in the worldwide rankings and it influences the popularity of your own assignments.
            </li>
            <br/>
            <li class="{style.content}">
                <b>Step 4: Create assignments!</b> Use the the <a href="#create">Create</a>-Tab to share your ideas.
                Your assignments will start with a certain reward (XP) based on your current level.
                Assignments are always sorted by reward, so it's important to reach a high reward if you want your ideas to be popuplar.
                Luckily, other users can boost your assignments with their own reward value if they like your idea,
                so you can start creating even if you're still at level 1. Also, creating really pays off:
                You get 10% of each reward that is issued to people who complete your assignment.
            </li>
        </ul>
    </g:HTMLPanel>
</ui:UiBinder>